caselogic.com 2010-06-22

# CD Cases, DVD Cases, MP3 Cases, Laptop Cases, Camera Cases, CD Wallets, DVD Wallets, iPod Cases, Laptop Sleeves - Case Logic

Home › Help Center › Privacy

## Our Privacy Policy

Last Updated: 7/14/05; We understand and share your concern about privacy. We want to assure you that Case Logic and its vendors (collectively, "Case Logic" or "We" or "Our") respect your privacy and treat your personal information with the highest commercially reasonable standards of safety, security and confidentiality. To better protect your privacy, We provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. If you have questions regarding this Policy, you may direct them to [help@online.caselogic.com](mailto:help@online.caselogic.com).

  * What information does Case Logic collect?
  * Our use of your information
  * Does Case Logic share the information it receives?
  * Accessing and updating your information
  * Security
  * A special note about children's privacy
  * Privacy Policy changes
  * Contacting Case Logic with question or comments

## What type of information does Case Logic collect?

Our goal is to provide you with a safe and enjoyable shopping experience. When We collect information about you it is in an effort to make our products and services more efficient and customized to you. You are free to browse the Case Logic site without revealing any personal information about yourself. However, once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us.

**Automatic Information**  

We automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on our site. We use this information to analyze our users' behavior, interests, and demographics to better understand and serve our shoppers. This information may include the URL that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your IP address.

**What about Cookies?**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that a web site will store on your computer's hard drive. Case Logic will use cookies to identify you during your session, make our services easier to use and to store items in your shopping cart between visits. Cookies are never used to store sensitive customer information such as names, addresses, credit card numbers or passwords. Acceptance of cookies is not a requirement to browse our site, however our shopping cart does require the acceptance of cookies to work properly. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can configure your browser to prevent that. If you would like to place an order on our site but object to or otherwise are unable to use cookies, please feel free to place your order via our toll free number: 1.888.666.5780 

**Personally Identifiable Information**  
This is information that you provide to us that is specific to you. We collect information such as your name, phone number, billing information, shipping information and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout our site. You provide such information when you make a purchase, enter a contest or sweepstakes, fill out a survey or form, provide ratings or testimonials feedback, give or redeem a gift certificate, as applicable. Where possible, We indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You can always choose not to provide information, but you may not be able to use a particular service or feature.

## Our use of your information

We use the information We collect from you to improve our products and services and make your shopping experience more efficient and relevant. We review the actions of our visitors on an aggregate basis to determine customers' preferences. Case Logic also conducts analysis and research on our visitors' demographics, interests, and pages viewed based on the information provided to us during ordering, from our server log files, contests or surveys.

**Contests and Sweepstakes**  
When you enter a contest or other promotion, We may ask you for contact information such as your name, address and e-mail address in order to administer the contest, to send you promotional e-mails, notify winners and make the winners' list publicly available pursuant to certain states' laws. As a condition of receiving any prize, you will be required to complete, execute and return an Affidavit of Eligibility, a Liability Release, and where lawful, a Publicity Release, for us to ensure that you are eligible to receive the prize according to the Contest Rules. In cases where the sweepstakes or promotional offer is co-branded with or sponsored by another party, We may share your information to that party. Your consent to such promotional use and disclosure of this information is a condition of your participation.

**E-mails**  
It is possible to register as a Case Logic email subscriber directly from our site or through another source, such as a Case Logic sweepstakes hosted on another site or the co-registration network. Upon registering, We will periodically send you newsletters and e-mails featuring exclusive sales, promotions and other members-only benefits. If you make a purchase on our site We will send you an order and shipping confirmation email. If you are a subscribed member, We will also send you emails to collect ratings and testimonials feedback related to your purchase. If you'd rather not receive emails, please visit the Your Account page to change your preferences.

**Fulfillment**  
During the purchase process, We will share your information with certain intermediaries (e.g. UPS, or Cybercash) strictly to process and ship your order.

**Promotional Offers**  
At times We may present or send offers to select Case Logic subscribers on behalf of other parties. When We do this, We do not give that company your personally identifiable information without your consent. If you do not want to receive such communications, please edit your account preferences at the Your Account section of the web site.

**Agents**  
We employ other third parties to perform services or functions on our behalf in order to improve our site, merchandising, marketing and promotional efforts, communications or other services. Those third parties include authorized contractors, consultants and other companies working with us (collectively, "agents"). They only have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, and may not share any personal information with others or use it for any other purpose than improving Case Logic services and offerings. If you have made a purchase on the Case Logic website, We may make your name and postal address available to pre-screened companies who have specific direct mail (e.g. catalog) product or service offers that We think may be of interest to you. We only share with these pre-screened companies the individual names and postal address of customers who have actually purchased products from us. If you do not want us to share your name and postal address information, simply follow the instructions in the section below titled "Accessing and Updating Your Information." We may also receive information about you from other sources (such as demographic information and purchase history) and add it to our information in order to make our marketing efforts more efficient.

**Advertisers**  
We work with third party advertising companies, such as Atlas DMT, to serve and track our ads. These third parties may serve other cookies. Our advertising partners use the anonymous, non-personally identifying information they collect from our site, in the aggregate, to help us better market and serve our customers. In the event that our advertisers collect any personal information on our behalf, it will not be used by them or disclosed to any third parties.

**Third Party Sites**  
You may visit other web sites, through links on our site, who may collect, use and share your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. The information practices of those websites linking from or to our site are not covered by this Policy, and We encourage you to be very cautious before you disclose your personal information to others. If you register for Case Logic on another web site or use a web site providing a service for Case Logic, that web site may provide personal information about you and your transactions back to Case Logic. It is possible that Case Logic could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such an event occur, you should expect that Case Logic would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide such products and services. Notice of such an event will be posted and We will require that the new combined entity follow practices which are substantially the same as the practices disclosed in this Privacy Policy until such time as a revision to this Privacy Policy is posted.

**Legal Requests**  
Case Logic will cooperate with law enforcement inquiries. Case Logic reserves the right to disclose any activities or information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as We, in our sole discretion, determine necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability. In addition, We may be required to provide personal information in response to a valid court order, subpoena, government investigation, or as otherwise required by law. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activity that We, in good faith, believe to be unlawful. We may release certain personal information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves. We may also release personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event.

## Accessing and Updating Your Information

You always have the opportunity to review and change the information you provide to us by logging into the site and entering in the new information yourself. You can edit your name, contact information and preferences by logging into the Your Account section of the site.

As a customer, subscriber, or contest entrant, you will occasionally receive e-mail communications about new Case Logic products, special offers We think you'll like and requests for feedback. If you want to stop receiving our emails or to specify the communications you prefer to receive, you may unsubscribe or edit your profile at any time. You can do this through any of our emails, by visiting your account preferences page in the Your Account section of this web site or sending us an email at [help@online.caselogic.com](mailto:help@online.caselogic.com).

You may ask to have your account information removed from our active databases; however, because We keep track of past purchases, you cannot delete information associated with past purchases. Such information will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible based on your account activity. Also, as a security measure We "back up" the data stored on our systems, and such prior information cannot be completely removed from our databases. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

## Security

The Case Logic Security Statement protects you while you shop at Case Logic. We guarantee that every transaction you make at Case Logic will be safe. This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your credit card as a result of shopping at Case Logic. The Case Logic Security Statement describes the security measures we take to prevent unauthorized access to your credit card information. Case Logic servers use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an encryption technology that works with Netscape, Microsoft Internet Explorer, and AOL's browser, so that only Case Logic can read a buyer's personal information. We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. However, We will transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

## A special note about children's privacy

You must be at least 18 years old to have our permission to use this site. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personally Identifiable Information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with your parents or guardians.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Case Logic reserves the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Policy at any time. Any changes will be posted in this document and will become effective immediately upon being posted unless We tell you otherwise.

## Your Consent

By using our web site, you consent to our use of information that is collected or submitted as described in this online Privacy Policy as modified from time to time.

## Contacting Case Logic

If you have further questions about Case Logic Privacy Policy or comments on how We can improve the Case Logic shopping experience, please do not hesitate to email us at [help@online.caselogic.com](mailto:help@online.caselogic.com).

Need more help? You can refer to our Help Center or email one of our friendly Customer Help Specialists at [help@online.caselogic.com](mailto:help@online.caselogic.com).

You may also write to us at:  
Privacy Manager  
Case Logic, Inc.  
5500 Greenwood Plaza Blvd.  
Suite 160  
Greenwood Village, CO 80111

We always enjoy hearing from you and appreciate your business.
